All right,they got water, orange juice...
好，他们有水，柳橙汁…
...and what looks like cider.
这个看起来像苹果汁
Taste it.
喝喝看吧
Yeah,it's fat.
对，这是一杯油
I drank fat!
我喝了油！
I know,I did that two minutes ago.
我知道，两分钟前我才喝过的
Hey,Mr. Tux.
穿燕尾服的先生
-Why aren't you dressed? -We have a half-hour.
你怎么还没换衣服？ 还有半小时
That was four minutes ago. We have to be out the door at 7:40.
那是四分钟前的事 我们必须在七点四十出门
Relax,we'll be ready. It takes us two minutes to get dressed.
放心，我们会准备好的 我们只要两分钟就着装完毕
I'd feel better if you got dressed now.
若你现在就换好，我会高兴点
-Okay. -Okay.
好 好
Oh,look at you. All sexy.
看看你，多性感啊
Really?
真的吗？
-How come you didn't come over earlier? -Because I'm a stupid,stupid man.
你怎么不早点过来？ 因为我真是笨得要命
Hey,Ross,want some cider?
罗斯，要不要来点苹果汁？
No.
不要
So you're pretty close,huh?
你快准备好了吧
Makeup's on. Hair's done.
妆化好了，头发梳好了
I just have to get dressed.
我只要换衣服就好了
And that takes,what? Just 6 or 7 minutes?
大概只要6或7分钟吧
Yeah. Once I figure out what I'm wearing.
是啊，只要我决定好要穿什么
Glass of fat?
要不要喝点油？
The One Where No One's Ready
本集播出：“准备出门”
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 河马压缩制作 本字幕为河马根据R3DVD OCR得来
What's the matter? You nervous about your speech?
怎么了？你是不是 因为要演讲而紧张？
Nope.
不是
-You wanna hear it? -Am I in it?
你要不要听听看？ 里面有提到我吗？
After I thank everyone for donating to the museum...
等我感谢完 所有捐钱给博物馆的人
... I sing a song about the wonder that is Joey.
我就唱一首歌 歌颂乔伊的伟大
Hello! You look great!
嗨，你看起来真棒
Thank you. I know,though.
谢谢你 虽然我已经知道了
You see this? This is a person who is ready to go.
看到没？ 这个人准备好，可以出发了
Phoebe,you....
菲比，你…
You are my star.
你真是我的偶像啊
Well,you're my lucky penny.
那你就是我的幸运铜板
All right,I took the quiz. And it turns out I do put career before men.
好吧，我做了心理测验 结果是我认为男人比事业重要
Get up.
起来
What?
什么？
-You're in my seat. -How is this your seat?
你坐在我的位子上 为何这是你的位子？
I was sitting there.
因为我刚才坐在这里
But then you left.
但是你离开了
Well,it's not like I went to Spain.
拜托，我又不是去多远的地方
I went to the bathroom. You knew I'd be back.
我是去厕所 你明知道我会回来的
What's the big deal? Sit somewhere else!
那有什么大不了的 去坐别的地方嘛
The "big deal" is I was sitting there last! So...
真正大不了的就是 我是最后坐在这里的人
...it's my seat.
所以这是我的位子
Well,actually,the last place you were sitting was in there,so....
事实上，你最后坐的地方 就是那里，所以…
You guys,you know what? It doesn't matter.
各位，你们知道嘛？ 那个一点都不重要
You both have to go get dressed before the big vein in my head pops.
你们俩都必须 在我脑血管爆掉前换好衣服
I just have to do one thing. It's not a big deal.
我只要再做一件事 这真的没什么大不了
Get up!
起来！
Phoebe,you look great!
菲比，你看起来好美
All right already.
好啦，早知道了
Are you gonna do magic?
你要变魔术吗？
That's funny. Change.
真好笑，给我换衣服去
-Hang on,I just got in. -I don't care.
慢点，我才刚进门 我才不管
It starts at 8. We can't be late.
晚会八点开始，我们不能迟到
"He could not,would not, want to wait."
他不能等，也不愿意等
Our table is down in front. My boss will be there.
我们的桌子在前方 我老板也会在那儿
Everyone will see if we arrive after it starts.
若晚会开始后我们才进场 大家都看得到
Has somebody been drinking my fat?
有人喝过我这一杯油吗？
Does this look like something a paleontologist's girlfriend would wear?
这像是古生物学家的女友 会穿的衣服吗？
I don't know. You might be the first one.
我不知道 你大概是首开先例吧
-Rach,did you check the machine? -No.
瑞秋，你听答录机留言了吗？ 没有
Wait. This is the outfit that makes my calves look fat. Never mind.
等等，这件衣服 会显得我小腿很粗，算了
Well,Joey,I wrote a little song today.
乔伊，我今天写了一首歌
It's called,"Get up!"
歌名叫做“起来”
All right. You can have the chair.
好啦，椅子给你啦
-Really? -Oh,my. Would you look at that?
真的？ 天啊，你看看这个
It's me,I'm coming over.
是我，我正要过去
What if I'm already there when you play this message?
若你播放这则留言时 我已经到了呢？
Is that too spooky?
是不是很诡异？
Hi,Rach,are you there? It's me. Pick up.
瑞秋，你在不在？ 是我，快接起来
Rachel? Rach?
瑞秋…？
What?
干嘛？
Never mind.
没事
Monica,it's Richard. Call me.
摩妮卡，我是理查 打电话给我
Is that message old or new?
这则留言是新的还是旧的？
Old or new? Old or new?
新的还是旧的…？
It's definitely old. Didn't you hear the double beep?
绝对是旧的 你没听到两声哔吗？
What if it's new? We agreed not to talk.
若是新的怎么办？ 我们说好不连络的
It could be important. Shouldn't I call him back?
可能有重要的事 我该不该回电话？
Honey,you did call him back. It's old.
甜心，你已经打过了 这是旧的留言
Yeah,see,Mon,listen. Listen.
是啊，摩妮卡，你听着…
When Carol and I broke up...
当卡萝与我分手时
... I went through the same thing. You know what I did?
我也经历一样的事 你知道我怎么做吗？
I got dressed.
我去换好衣服
Really,really quickly,okay? Okay?
真的要快一点，真的 好…
There we go. There we go.
这就对了…
You know what? Don't get up. Just sit there.
你知道吗？别起来了 就坐在那里吧
I just hope you don't mind my hand right here.
只希望你别介意我的手 放在这里
Not touching. Can't get mad! Not touching. Can't get mad!
没碰到，不能生气 没碰到，不能生气
Not touching. Can't get mad!
没碰到，不能生气
Oh,my God!
我的天啊
You rotten boys!
你们这些坏孩子！
-Sorry,Phoebe. -What am I gonna do?
抱歉，菲比 我该怎么办？
Don't rub it! What gets out hummus?
别乱抹 有什么可以去除豆泥？
What gets out hummus?
有什么可以去除豆泥？
Monica! What gets out hummus?
摩妮卡！ 有什么可以去除豆泥？
If it is a new message, what is he calling to say?
如果那个留言是新的 他到底打来说什么？
Okay,thanks. Yeah,I'll try that.
好，谢谢，我会试试看的
Maybe he called to say you're obsessive and crazy?
说不定他打来说 你执迷不悟而且太疯狂
-So should I call him back? -No!
我该不该回电话给他？ 不！
No!
不！
-Fine,we'll both sit in the chair. -Fine with me.
很好，我们一起坐在椅子上 随便啊
I am so comfortable.
我好舒服啊
Me too.
我也是
In fact,I think I might be a little too comfortable.
事实上，我可能有点太舒服了
Okay,we have 19 minutes. I want you to go and change.
好，我们有19分钟 钱德，我要你去换衣服
When you come back,Joey will go change and he'll have vacated the chair.
等你回来后，乔伊去换衣服 他就会把椅子空出来
-Okay. -All right.
好 好的
Fine. I'm going.
好，我要走了
When I get back,it's Chair City. And I'm the guy...
等我回来后这里就是 椅子王国，而我是…
...who's sitting in a chair!
坐在椅子上的那个人！
Is this a little too
这是不是有点太…
Pheebs? What happened?
菲比，怎么回事？
I got the hummus.
我沾到豆泥了
Oh,honey,we'll find you something. You wanna wear my black jacket?
甜心，我们会找出衣服给你 你要不要穿我的黑外套？
-lt won't go with this dress. -You're right.
这样跟洋装就不能搭配了 没错
-Well,let's just get you out of that. -No,no,no. Not "out of that."
来吧我们把衣服换掉 不…可别换掉
-Not "out" of clothes. -Can Phoebe borrow your green dress?
千万别把衣服脱掉 菲比可以借你的绿洋装穿吗？
I called him.
我打给他了
Yes. I got his machine and I left a message.
对，我进入他的答录机 然后我留言了
But it's okay. It's okay...
不过没关系…
... because it was,like, a casual,breezy message.
因为那是个随兴，轻松的留言
It was breezy.
很轻松
Oh,God,what if it wasn't breezy?
天啊，若听起来并不轻松 该怎么办？
How could it not be breezy? No. Because you're in such a breezy place.
怎么可能不轻松？ 不会，这里是个轻松的地方
I got it. I'll play my message and you guys tell me if it's breezy enough.
我知道了，我播放我的留言 你们再告诉我是否轻松
But how you gonna do that?
你怎么可能那样做？
I know the code to his answering machine.
我知道他答录机的密码
Okay,Mon,I really don't think this is the
好，摩妮卡 我不认为现在应该…
Okay,you're dialing. You are dialing.
好，你在拨号了…
Hi,this is Richard. Please leave a message at the tone.
我是理查 请在哔声后留言
You have two new messages.
你有两个新讯息
What a cool job.
真是个好工作
"You have two new messages."
“你有两个新讯息”
Please pass the pie.
“请把派递给我”
Hi,it's Monica. I'm just checking in.
我是摩妮卡 我只是想确定一下
I got a message and didn't know if it was old or new.
我有一通留言 不知道是新的还是旧的
So I'm just checking.
所以，我只是问问看
So let me know.
告诉我吧
Or don't. Whatever.
或者不告诉我，都可以
I'm breezy!
我很轻松
You can't say you're "breezy." That negates the "breezy."
你不能说“我很轻松” 这样就不轻松了嘛
Hola. It's me. Yesterday was really fun.
你好啊，是我 昨天真是愉快
Call me about this weekend,okay?
打电话给我 谈谈周末的计划，好吗？
Now,she sounded breezy.
看，她听起来就很轻松
He's seeing someone. I can't believe he's seeing someone.
他开始约会了 我真不敢相信他开始约会
-You don't know that. -Well,whose voice was that?
你又不知道那个是谁 那么那是谁的声音？
Maybe it was his sister's. Maybe it was his daughter's.
说不定是他妹妹的 说不定是他女儿的
Michelle. Of course! Did it sound like Michelle?
蜜雪儿，一定是了！ 听起来像蜜雪儿吗？
Oh,great. It's starting to rain. That'll make it easier to get a cab.
太好了，开始下雨了 这样计程车又更难叫了
It was Michelle.
是蜜雪儿
It was definitely Michelle.
绝对是蜜雪儿
Try Monica's green dress. If it doesn't fit,wear my gray silk one.
去试穿摩妮卡的绿洋装 不适合就穿我的灰色丝质洋装
-Unless I wear it. -You don't know what you're wearing?
那我要穿那件？ 你还不知道自己要穿什么？
I'm just trying to look nice for your big night.
今晚是你的大日子 我只是希望自己好看一点
Yeah,which we have to leave for in 12 minutes.
是啊，而我们在12分钟内 必须出门
Come on,I'll just pick something out for you.
来吧，我帮你选衣服
You'll notice that I'm fully dressed.
你看到了，我全换好了
I,in turn,have noticed that you are not.
而我呢，也发现你 什么都还没换
So in the words of A.A. Milne, "Get out of my chair,dill-hole."
所以，套小熊维尼作者的话 “离开我的椅子，驴蛋！”
Okay.
好
-What are you doing? -You said to give you the chair.
你在干什么？ 你叫我离开椅子啊
You didn't say anything about cushions.
你又没说不能带走椅垫
They're the essence of the chair!
但椅垫是椅子的精华所在
That's right! I'm taking the essence.
没错，我要带走精华
Oh,he'll be back.
他会回来的
Oh,there's nobody in the room.
这里什么人也没有
-I'm sorry,I thought it looked pretty. -That was a Halloween costume.
对不起，我觉得这样很美 这是万圣节服装
Unless you would like me to go as Little Bo Peep.
除非你要我穿的像 小牧羊女一样？
I didn't recognize it without that inflatable sheep.
若没有那只可充气的羊 我还真认不出来
Yeah,which,by the way,Chandler, I would like back one of these days.
是啊，对了，钱德 我最近想要一只回来
Rach,good! Listen,isn't this perfect for me?
瑞秋，很好啊 这件是不是很适合我？
Oh,it's perfect! But not for tonight.
太棒了！ 但是不适合今晚
Of course,not for tonight. Hi. I'm going to a benefit.
当然不适合今晚 我要参加慈善晚会呢
Not for tonight? What are you doing?
不适合今晚？ 那你在干嘛？
No,I'm sorry. We didn't mean it. I love you. Breathe.
对不起，不是故意的 我爱你…深呼吸
We used them as pillows when we went camping.
我们去露营时 把它们当枕头
What?
什么？
The sheep.
那些羊啊
Hey,what you do on your own time....
你的闲虾时间在干嘛…
Where's my underwear?
我的内裤呢？
-Come on,you took his underwear? -He took my essence!
拜托，你拿了他的内裤？ 他拿走我的精华啊
Okay,hold on. Why can't you just wear the underwear you're wearing now?
好，等等，你干嘛不穿 你身上的内裤？
Because I'm not wearing any underwear now.
因为我现在根本没有穿内裤
Then why do you have to wear underwear tonight?
那你今晚为何要穿内裤？
It's a rented tux,okay?
因为这燕尾服是用租的
I'm not gonna go commando in another man's fatigues.
我不想没穿内裤 就穿别人的衣服
Then somebody's gonna have to give somebody back his cushions.
那有人就得把椅垫还给别人
Okay. You hide my clothes,I'm gonna do the exact opposite to you.
好，你把我衣服藏起来 我要做一件完全相反的事
What,are you gonna show me my clothes?
什么？难道你要 给我看我的衣服吗？
Hey,opposite...
相反的事…
...is opposite.
就是相反的事
He's got nothing!
他什么都没有！
Okay,I'm ready.
好，我准备好了
Rachel didn't have anything I liked but this ribbon.
瑞秋那儿没有我喜欢的 除了这个圣诞彩带
I thought,all right, I'll be political.
我想，好吧 那我就政治化一点罗
-What are you supporting? -Christmas.
那你在支持什么？ 当然是耶诞节
Hey,that's okay with me. Two down, and I have exactly 12 minutes
我无所谓，已经搞定两个了 我还有整整12分钟
What?
什么？
My watch stopped. My watch. Okay,see...
我的表停了 我的表，好，你看…
...the dinosaur tail isn't going around anymore.
这个恐龙指针的尾巴不动了
What time is it? It's 7:33. I have 7 minutes.
现在几点？已经7点33分 我还有7分钟
I have seven minutes!
我还有7分钟！
Which shoes should I wear? The black or the purple?
我该穿哪一双鞋？ 黑色的还是紫色的？
-Just pick one,okay? -Oh,okay,okay. The black.
随便挑一双，好吗？ 好啦，黑色的
Do you have black with little strappies?
你有没有黑色的 然后有细带子的？
Yeah. But those go better with pants. Maybe I should wear pants.
有，不过那种适合配裤子 或者我该穿裤子
Yeah,pants! What an idea! Or better yet,go without pants.
对了，穿裤子是好主意 或者不要穿裤子更好
I don't know what you're doing, but just get in there...
我不知道你在做什么 但是你快进去…
...and pick out any shoes that fit your feet.
找出随便一双可以穿的鞋子
I don't care if they match. I don't care if they make...
我不管它是否搭配 我不管它是否会…
...your ankles or your knees or your earlobes look fat. Just do it!
让你的脚踝，膝盖，或耳垂 看起来胖胖的，快去吧
Go in there,pick something out so we can go.
进去房间里，挑出要穿的 然后我们就可以走了
-All right. -Thank you.
好的 谢谢你
I've got to call Michelle to see if that was her voice.
我要打给蜜雪儿 确定那是她的声音，抱歉
It was. It was her voice.
没错，那就是她的声音
Monica,I think you've gone over to the bad place.
摩妮卡，我想你又开始偏执了
Hola.
（西班牙语）喂？
Hello? Hello?
喂…？
-Okay. That was her,right? -Definitely. Yeah.
好，那是她的声音，对吗？ 绝对是，对啊
So there you go.
这样就解决啦
We're out of the woods. I think I'll get dressed now.
我们的危险解除啦 我要去换衣服了
-I'll get it. -Okay.
我来接 好
Hi,Monica and Rachel's.
你好，摩妮卡与瑞秋的家
Yeah,just a second. Can I ask who's calling?
好，请稍等 请问您是哪位？
It's Michelle!
是蜜雪儿！
She must have that "caller l. D." thing. You should get that.
她一定有来电显示功能 你也该去装一个
Michelle?
蜜雪儿？
Yeah,that was me. I dialed your number by mistake.
对，就是我 我不小心拨了你的电话
Just try to be
只要试着…
You're so sweet.
你真的好帖心
Yeah,we were a great couple.
是啊，我们是一对很好的情侣
I know,I really miss him.
我知道，我真的很想他
Well,you know how it is. It's just that....
你也知道的嘛 只不过…
You know what's weird?
你知道奇怪的是什么？
Donald Duck never wore pants.
唐老鸭从来不穿裤子
But when he gets out of the shower...
但是当他洗完澡出来…
... he always puts a towel around his waist.
他总是在腰间围上一条毛巾
I mean,what is that about?
我是说，那算什么？
I only beeped in so I could hear my own message.
蜜雪儿，我只是进入信箱 来听我自己的留言
I mean,that's allowed.
那样总可以吧
I would really appreciate it if you wouldn't tell your dad about
我真的希望你别告诉你爸…
What do you mean,you don't feel comfortable with this? We're friends!
你说你不高兴是什么意思？ 我们是朋友呢
That bitch always hated me.
那个小婊子根本就讨厌我
I'm calling her back.
我要再打给她
-Okay,fine. -Okay.
好，好啊 好
-She's got a phone in there,right? -Okay,we're on it.
她房间里有电话吧？ 好，我们来处理吧
I know it says "black tie optional"...
我知道单子上写 “打领带与否，自行决定”
... but this may be pushing it a little.
但这样会不会太过分了点？
I'm not gonna go.
我不去了
You're not gonna go?
你不去了？
No,I think I'm gonna catch up on my correspondence.
不，我想更新我的通讯录
How can you not be going?
你怎么可以不去呢？
I'm not gonna go.
我就是不去了
So I think that will accomplish the "not going."
我想这样就表明了 “我不去”的意思
You know,just out of curiosity
我只是好奇…
Ever since I was humiliated and yelled at in front of my friends...
自从你在我朋友面前 羞辱我，又对我大吼
... I'm just,I don't know,not in a very museum benefit-y kind of mood.
我就没有情绪去参加 什么博物馆的慈善会了
Right. Well,okay. Okay. God,I'm sorry. I'm sorry I yelled.
好…天啊，很抱歉 我对你大吼大叫，对不起
-That's fine. -No,but you're mad.
没关系 不，可是你在生气
I'm not mad. I'm just not going.
我没有生气，我只是不去了
-Right. -Okay.
是的 好
You know that I have to go,right?
你知道我一定要去吧？
So is it gonna be,like, I'm abandoning you while you're upset?
那这样会不会变成 我在你难过时离你而去？
-No. -No?
不会 不会？
-You're not upset about the yelling. -Right. And the humiliating.
我对你大吼，你不难过？ 对，还包括你的羞辱
Well,of course,the humiliating.
当然罗，还有羞辱
So we...
那么，我们…
...we're okay?
我们之间没问题？
-We're good. -Right.
我们很好啊 好
-Honey? I love you. -Yes,Ross.
甜心，我爱你 是的，罗斯
Get away from that phone!
把电话放下！
She's just getting dressed now.
她已经开始换衣服了
Is it wrong that I was totally aroused by that?
我居然因此而兴奋 我是不是有问题？
Okay,buddy boy,here it is.
好啦，兄弟，就是这样啦
You hide my clothes, I'm wearing everything you own.
你把我衣服藏起来 我就把你所有的衣服穿上
Oh,my God!
我的天啊
That is so not the opposite of taking somebody's underwear!
我把你的内裤藏起来 但这根本不是相反的事
Look at me! I'm Chandler.
你看看我，我是钱德！
Could I be wearing any more clothes?
我还能再多穿一件衣服吗？
Maybe if I wasn't going commando....
或许我不该不穿内裤的…
It's hot with all this stuff on.
穿这么多真是热死我了
I better not do any, I don't know,lunges.
我最好别再做些运动… 像是蹲马步之类的
Okay,enough. Enough with the lunging.
够了，别再蹲马步了
I'm sick of this. I've had it up to here.
我快被烦死了 我真的已经受够了
Neither of you can come to the party!
你们两个都不准参加晚会！
Jeez,what a baby!
天啊，真幼稚
Way to ruin it. I was just gonna go get dressed.
你干嘛破坏一切 我正要去换衣服了
The only person I cared about getting dressed...
那个唯一我会在乎 她是否换好衣服的人
...is the person who's not even gonna go.
却是那个不肯去的人
Look,Rach,I'm sorry,okay?
瑞秋，我很抱歉，好吗？
Look,I was a jerk,okay? I'm sorry I yelled. I want you there.
我真是个混球 抱歉对你大吼，我希望你能去
I need you there.
我需要你去
What can I do to show you how much I want you to be there?
要怎样做才能证明 我有多希望你去？
You could drink the fat.
你可以把那杯油喝掉
Welcome to an adult conversation.
欢迎你进入大人的谈话世界
No,no,no. Now wait a minute. Wait a minute.
不，等一下…
-That actually sounds interesting. -What?
听起来挺有意思的 什么？
I think you should drink the fat.
我想你应该把那杯油喝掉
Okay,if that's what it takes to show you how much you mean to me...
好，若这样就能证明 你对我有多重要…
...and how much I want you there, that's what I'll do.
以及我多希望你能去 那我就愿意去做
Let me get you another glass. That's been sitting out.
我帮你换一个杯子 这一杯放好久了
I think this will be fine.
我想这样可以了
Okay,vanilla milkshake. Just a vanilla milkshake...
好吧，香草奶昔 只不过是香草奶昔…
...with chicken bits floating in it.
只不过有鸡肉的碎屑浮着
Cheers.
干杯！
No,don't! Okay,okay,I'll go. I'll go.
不，不要 好吧，我去就是了…
You will?
你肯去？
You were really gonna do that.
你真的会那么做，对吧？
Well,yeah.
是啊
You were gonna drink the fat.
你真的愿意喝下那些油？
Let's see what else he'll do!
我们来看看他还能做什么
How about you get changed? Give him his underwear.
不如你现在去换衣服 你把他的内裤还给他
I'll get a cab. I want everyone downstairs in two minutes.
我来叫计程车 我要大家在两分钟内下楼
Monica!
摩妮卡！
Stop it.
别做了！
Stop it!
别再做了！
Ross went to get a cab,so we
罗斯去叫计程车了 那么我们…
What are you doing? No,Monica,no!
你在做什么？ 不，摩妮卡！
Hi,this is Richard.
我是理查
You have three new messages.
你有三个新讯息
Not anymore.
再也没有了
Message erased.
讯息已删除
To record your message, begin speaking at the tone.
请在哔声后留言
Hi,Richard. It's Monica.
你好，理查，我是摩妮卡
Listen,I did something kind of crazy tonight.
我今晚做了一件很疯狂的事
Maybe I'm getting my period or something. I don't know.
或许我“那个”快来了 我也不晓得
Anyway,I beeped into your machine and I heard this message...
反正我进入你的答录机 然后听到一个留言…
...that freaked me out...
快把我搞疯了
...and Michelle will tell you the rest.
其他的蜜雪儿会告诉你
I'm sorry,okay? And I hope that we can just forget the whole thing.
我很抱歉 我希望你忘了这整件事
Your outgoing message has now been changed.
你的主人留言已经更改
Outgoing?
主人留言？
Did that say outgoing?
他刚刚是说主人留言？
Not outgoing!
不是主人留言！
Hi,Richard,it's Monica.
你好，理查，我是摩妮卡
Listen,I did something kind of crazy tonight.
我今晚做了一件疯狂的事
Maybe I'm getting my period or something. I don't know.
或许我“那个”快来了 我也不晓得
-How did you do that? -I don't know!
你是怎么做的？ 我不知道！
Goodbye.
再见
Okay,I've got two cabs and no people! Go,go,go!
好，我叫到两辆计程车 但还没人坐进去，快！
Maybe we can call the phone company to change the message?
或许我们可以 叫电话公司改掉那个留言？
They could change his number.
他们可以把他的电话号码改掉
I think after this, he'll be doing that himself.
我想经过这件事 他会自己处理了
Rachel!
瑞秋！
You.... You look....
你…你看起来…
And I still have about five seconds to spare.
而我还剩下五秒钟
That was about 7 seconds.
这样大概花掉七秒钟
So we're a little late.
所以我们迟了一点
Come on.
走吧
Oh,and by the way....
对了…
What?
什么事？
I'm going commando too.
我里面也没穿…
Dr. Geller?
盖勒博士？
-Sherman Whitfield,London lnstitute. -What a pleasure.
我是伦敦来的雪曼惠菲 很荣幸见到你
I was quite impressed with your paper on pre-Cretaceous fossils.
你的前白垩纪化石报告 写得真不错
Yes. It confirmed everything I'd written.
是的，你再次验证了 我以前写的东西
Excuse me.
对不起
Hi.
你好
Yes?
什么事？
You're kind of sitting in my seat.
你好像坐在我的位子上
What do you mean,your seat?
你说你的位子 是什么意思？
-I mean,I was sitting there. -But you got up.
我是说，我本来坐在这儿 但是你起来了
But I never left the room.
可是我没有离开这个房间
But you left the chair area.
但是你离开椅子了
All right,that's it. Give me your underwear.
好吧，就这样 把你的内裤给我